Records of the Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1975-2002 M1354
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Materials related to Peru, Colombia, and Canada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 295)
- Materials related to Peru, Paraguay, Cuba, Caribbean region, Costa Rica, Colombia, and Chile (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 296)
- Materials related to Peru and Paraguay (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 297)
- Materials related to Peru (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous subject files ("1988 U.S. Drug Law," "Election - U.S. President '08," etc.). (Box 298)
- Miscellaneous subject files - "Drugs," "Democrats '84-85," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 299)
- Miscellaneous publications ("Ecuador," "Tiempos del Mundo," "Global Review," "Sunday Mirror," newsletters, etc.); subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 300)
- Miscellaneous subject files ("El Niño," "Educational Programs / seminars," etc.); personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 301)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Honduras; subject files - "Debt," "Education," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 302)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Honduras; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 303)
- Materials related to Nicaragua; miscellaneous subject files - "Op-Ed submissions," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 304)
- Materials related to Nicaragua; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 305)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Honduras; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 306)
- Materials related to Nicaragua; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 307)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Venezuela; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 308)
- Materials related to Venezuela and Uruguay; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 309)
- Materials related to Venezuela and Uruguay, continued; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 310)
- Materials related to Venezuela; subject files - "Hispanics," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 311)
- Materials related to Venezuela; subject files - "Human Rights," etc.; personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 312)
- Materials related to Venezuela and Uruguay; subject files - "Guerrillas," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 313)
- Materials related to Great Britain; subject files ("Human Rights," "Bilingual Education - Hispanics," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 314)
- Materials related to Chile; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 315)
- Materials related to Chile, mostly regarding economic issues (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 316)
- Materials related to Chile and Cayman Islands; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 317)
- Materials related to Chile, continued; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 318)
- Materials related to Chile, Argentina, Caribbean, Canada, Nicaragua; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 319)
- Materials related to Chile, Canada - U.S. relationships, Caribbean (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 320)
- Materials related to Chile, mostly regarding human rights, 1978-1985 (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 321)
- Materials related to Chile, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 322)
- Materials related to Chile, Canada, Malvinas (Falklands), Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 323)
- Materials related to Chile, Malvinas (Falklands), Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 324)
- Materials related to Chile and Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 325)
- Materials related to Malvinas (Falklands), Chile and Argentina, mostly regarding human rights (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 326)
- Materials related to Malvinas (Falklands), Chile and Argentina, continued; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 327)
- Materials related to Chile and Argentina, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 328)
- Materials related to Malvinas (Falklands), Chile and Argentina, Chile - Soviet Union relationships (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 329)
- Materials related to Malvinas (Falklands), Chile and Argentina, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 330)
- Materials related to Malvinas (Falklands) and Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 331)
- Materials related to Argentina, Cuba, Belize, Bolivia, Brazil, El Salvador; subject files - "Guerrillas," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 332)
- Materials related to Argentina, Brazil, Ecuador; subject files - "Guerrillas," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 333)
- Materials related to Argentina, Chile, Guatemala, Guyana, Haiti; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 334)
- Materials related to Argentina and Honduras (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 335)
- Materials related to Argentina and El Salvador; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 336)
- Materials related to Canada, Colombia, Caribbean; subject files - "Guerrillas 1979-1984" (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 337)
- Materials related to Argentina, Mexico, Dominican Republic (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 338)
- Materials related to Argentina, Ecuador, Nicaragua; subject files - "Guerrillas," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 339)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, France, Colombia (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 340)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, mostly regarding President Somoza (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 341)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Canada, Caribbean, Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 342)
- Materials related to Dominican Republic, Antigua, Chile, El Salvador, Colombia, Bolivia, Canada, and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 343)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Canada, Chile; subject files - "Contras," "Salmon," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 344)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Argentina, Brazil, Bolivia, Haiti, Panama, Peru, Cuba; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 345)
- Materials related to Colombia, Canada, Caribbean, Dominican Republic, Mexico; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 346)
- Materials related to Brazil and Chile; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 347)
- Materials related to Guatemala and Nicaragua; subject files - "Organization of American States - OAS," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 348)
- Materials related to Caribbean; subject files - "Bush Administration," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 349)
- Miscellaneous loose materials (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 350)
- Materials related to Canada and Nicaragua; subject files - "Rigs Bank," "Contras," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 351)
- Subject files, mostly regarding Nicaragua - U.S. relations; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 352)
- Subject files regarding Nicaragua - U.S. relations, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 353)
- Subject files regarding Nicaragua - U.S. relations, continued; materials related to Canada, Costa Rica, Panama, Uruguay; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 354)
- Materials related to Argentina, Brazil, Haiti, Bahamas, Paraguay, Peru (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 355)
- Materials related to Venezuela, Panama, Peru, Suriname, Paraguay; miscellaneous publications and subject files (clippings, leaflets, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 356)
- Materials related to Uruguay, Nicaragua, Argentina, Panama, Chile, Mexico, Paraguay, Puerto Rico, Suriname, Trinidad, Virgin Isles, West India; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 357)
- Materials related to Mexico, Colombia, and Chile; subject files - "U.S. Latin Policy, Jan. 1, 1989," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 358)
- Materials related to Mexico; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 359)
- Materials related to Colombia and Peru; subject files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 360)
- Materials related to Peru (mostly regarding the coup), Nicaragua, El Salvador; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 361)
- Materials related to Mexico, Brazil, and Peru; subject files - "NATO," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 362)
- Materials related to Mexico; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 363)
- Materials related to Mexico, continued; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 364)
- Subject and personal files - "Military," "Letelier," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 365)
- Materials related to Mexico, Canada, and Colombia; subject and personal files - "Liberal International," "Letelier," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 366)
- Materials related to Chile and Nicaragua; miscellaneous subject and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 367)
- Materials related to Honduras, Haiti - U.S. relationships; subject files - "Clinton," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 368)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Brazil, and Cuba; subject files - "Native Americans," "National Endowment for Democracy - NED," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 369)
- Materials related to Chile; subject files - "Latin America," "National Endowment for Democracy - NED," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 370)
- Materials related to Canada and El Salvador; subject files - "NED," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 371)
- Materials related to Honduras, Guatemala, and Jamaica; subject files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 372)
- Materials related to Costa Rica, Cuba, Dominican Republic, El Salvador, and Ecuador; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 373)
- Materials related to Dominican Republic and El Salvador; subject files - "Drugs," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 374)
- Materials related to Cuba; subject files - "Drugs, 1992," "Environment, Jan. 1989," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 375)
- Materials related to Cuba, Haiti, Guatemala, Grenada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 376)
- Materials related to Cuba and Nicaragua; subject files - "Environment," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous (clippings mostly). (Box 377)
- Subject files - "Latin America Studies Association," "Lawyers," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 378)
- Subject files - "Immigration Policy," "Inter-American Court for Human Rights," "Inter-American Defense College," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 379)
- Subject files - "Inter-American Development Bank," "Inter-American Foundation," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 380)
- Miscellaneous publications, typescripts, reports, correspondence, etc. (Box 381)
- Subject files ("Inter-Faith Center on Corporate Responsibility," "Indians," "Latin America - Trade Unions," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 382)
- Subject files - "Insurgent Groups," "International Lending Agencies," "Jewish," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 383)
- Materials related to Colombia; subject files - "International League for Human Rights," "Jews," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 384)
- Materials related to Israel; subject files - "Latin American Economic Trends," "Institute of the Americas," etc.; personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 385)
- Materials related to Jamaica; subject files - "Latin American Economic Trends," etc.; personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 386)
- Materials related to Jamaica and Guyana; subject files - "Latin American Debt," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 387)
- Materials related to Jamaica, Guyana, and El Salvador; subject files - "COHA - Interns," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 388)
- Materials related to El Salvador; subject files - "Democratic Revolutionary Fund," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 389)
- Materials related to Jamaica, Colombia, and El Salvador; subject files - "Election 1989," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 390)
- Materials related to Haiti and El Salvador; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 391)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Martinique, Guadeloupe, and El Salvador; subject files - "COHA - Press Releases," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 392)
- Materials related to El Salvador; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 393)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and El Salvador; subject files - "Latin America - Migration," etc.; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 394)
- Materials related to Haiti and El Salvador; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 395)
- Materials related to Haiti, mostly regarding human rights and elections; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 396)
- Materials related to Haiti, Vietnam, and El Salvador; subject files ("Women," "U.N. Development Program," "U.S. - Latin America," etc.); personal files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 397)
- Materials related to Haiti and Guatemala; subject files ("UNESCO - Financial," "Haiti and the CBI," etc.); personal files (mostly on 'W'); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 398)
- Subject files ("World Bank," "World Court," "World Federalist Association," etc.; personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 399)
- Materials related to Haiti, Paraguay, Peru, and the United States; subject files ("Women's League for Peace and Freedom," "Woodstock Theological Center," "Waste Exportation," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 400)
- Materials related to Chile and the United States; subject files ("U.S. Information Agency," etc.); personal files ("Kirkpatrick, Dew," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 401)
- Materials related to the United States; subject files ("Latin America - Trade Statistics," etc.); personal files, on 'L' and 'K' mostly (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 402)
- "Despachos" newsletter [?], Aug.-Sept. 1987, Nov.-Dec. 1988. (Box 403)
- Subject files ("Kissinger Commission," "Latin American Free Trade Market," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 404)
- "Despachos," Jan.-July 1988; other publications. (Box 405)
- Materials related to Nicaragua mostly (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); "Despachos," miscellaneous issues. (Box 406)
- Subject and personal files - "Kennedy," "King," "Labor," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous publications, etc. (Box 407)
- Subject files - "Drugs," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); the typescript "Reagan's Rampage" by Prof. Terrence E. Paupp, 1984; the newsletter "Daily Report. Annex - Latin America," Nov. 1988. (Box 408)
- Subject files ("Land Reform," "Labor," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 409)
- Materials related to Argentina; subject file ("1987 Central America, Peace Plan"); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 410)
- Materials related to Nicaragua; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 411)
- Materials related to Nicaragua; press releases; subject files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 412)
- Materials related to Haiti; subject files - "Research on Drugs," "Caribbean Projects," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 413)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Haiti; subject files - "Documents from Religious Groups," "Contadora, Spring 1986," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 414)
- Subject files ("Inflation," etc.); press releases; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 415)
- Materials related to Cuba, Nicaragua, and Haiti; subject files ("Spanish Language Documents," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 416)
- Materials related to Haiti; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 417)
- Materials related to Honduras, Guyana, and Haiti; subject files ("Labor and Free Trade, 1978-1979," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 418)
- Materials related to Argentina; subject files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 419)
- Materials related to Peru and Colombia; subject files - "Department of State Briefs," "Impunity," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 420)
- Materials related to Cuba, Mexico, and El Salvador; subject files - "Transafrica Forum," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 421)
- Subject files - "AIDS Caribbean," "Environment / World Bank," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous newspapers. (Box 422)
- Materials related to Paraguay; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 423)
- Materials related to Haiti (clippings, leaflets, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous publications. (Box 424)
- Materials related to Mexico and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); publications of the Inter-American Court of Human Rights, 1994; "Boletin de Noticias," 1991 issues; other publications. (Box 425)
- Subject files ("Food Aid," "Drugs - General," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 426)
- Subject files ("Indigenous Brazilians," "Free Trade," "Corruption in Latin America," etc.); COHA files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 427)
- Materials related to Guatemala and Paraguay; subject files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 428)
- Materials related to Panama; subject file ("Foreign Aid"); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 429)
- Materials related to Haiti, Guyana, and Jamaica; subject files ("Oil," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 430)